I didn't expect to see you so soon...
What a pleasant surprise, Kisaragi-san.
We'll be using your place as
our new headquarters, Seraphiel.
That's quite all right, but,
are you nearing your goal?
Only if you step out into the open.
There won't be a priest
to bless you if I die.
Perhaps I underestimated the current Emperor.
I won't set aside my final weapon any longer.
From now on, it's all hands on deck.
I'll kill them all.
So you'll be using the two
I introduced you to earlier?
Of course.
Whoa...
The moon's so pretty tonight.
Too bad we'll be too busy
to enjoy it starting tomorrow.
Let's get this over with as soon as possible.
Tasuketsu: Fate of the Majority
My, my.
Would you look at that!
If it isn't Kou-san from
the Three Powers himself.
What's up?
You two will be under
my constant surveillance.
Is that so? Go right ahead!
If I see anything suspicious,
consider yourselves dead.
Sure. Like I said, "Go right ahead!"
Who exactly are you, anyway?
How did you possess information
on the current Emperor?
I already told you!
We happened to meet each other
before fighting the Emperor.
Then why did you approach Seraphiel?
No one was supposed to know
about his relation to Lady Kisaragi.
Total coincidence!
I randomly passed by a church,
so I decided to pray that
I could serve the Queen,
when you guys suddenly showed up!
Never mind.
No matter your motive, no one
is a match before Lady Kisaragi.
Hmm...
"Before"... maybe.
We're off then.
Leave the skies to us.
They're not going with the dragon?
Maybe it's more stable.
Rika sacrificed her leg, so that makes sense.
When did she start walking without a cane?
Did you notice her left leg
became a prosthetic?
I actually tried to use my Fusion Right
to reconstruct her right leg,
but it didn't work for whatever reason.
So instead, we reconstructed her left leg
and moved it to her dominant right side.
And we used my Fusion Right to create
a special prosthetic for her left leg.
Wait! When did you learn to do
something so complicated?
What do you think we
were doing for a month?!
We weren't bumming
around the whole time!
Mm?
Oh yeah!
I totally forgot, but we actually
learned something big last month!
Oh yeah, that's right.
You can tell us while we're
preparing for the announcement.
So, we spent the month back
in my homeland, and...
We were researching itako.
Itako?
You mean those people that channel
dead spirits and speak for them and stuff?
That's when a question popped in my head.
How did the Rights come into existence?
They're supposedly
"a collection of human greed"
"that materialized due to a certain event".
Mediums!
Right. And to top it off...
Maybe if if a god or its subjects
existed, we could ask them.
God's Subjects
The words "God's subjects"
clicked in my mind.
Jin (God)
Omi (Subject)
It may just be coincidence, but
they're the same kanji as Omi's name.
But I didn't know anything. So that's why...
You went to Omi's homeland
to search for clues!
Itako use their bodies as mediums
to channel the dead and
connect them to this world.
Right
So the Rights might be manifested
through a medium of some sort, too?
Like the envelopes?
Mm-yup.
So if the dead are equivalent to the Rights,
and the bodies are the envelopes,
there's gotta be an "agent"
acting as the itako somewhere.
Could it be... the Queen?!
It's highly likely.
It's time!
Let's announce this, for real!
There will be a rule change for Stage Three.
Starting tomorrow at midnight,
Tokyo will be shut down.
No entry or exit will be
allowed after lockdown.
Stage Three will be suspended
to be resumed at a later date.
Tokyo on lockdown?
Kou. Gather all members.
As you wish.
Kou, stay at the East Warehouse
and continue remote surveillance
and communications.
Three minutes until midnight...
Use Meguru's Exchange Right
to transport to Tokyo.
All of you will attack.
I order you to annihilate
the current Emperor's army!
The Queen will launch an attack.
Prepare for battle.
Excuse me?!
I thought we were just gonna monitor them.
If they simply send someone
to Tokyo before the lockdown,
there's no need to face them in battle.
That's a scenario we
could easily win against.
But if the Queen realizes the true
meaning behind the lockdown,
it means she sees through to our motive.
As a countermeasure, she may go on the attack
and send out members in full force.
We could get chased
into a corner if that happens.
So we're better off fighting then...
Out of the enemies identified by Shinozaki,
we'll fight those we can beat first.
We'll slowly chip away at their forces.
It's kill or be killed.
Don't hesitate to kill them
if you want to win. Understand?
Shinozaki here. Confirming activity
at the prefecture border.
Most are civilians, but...
Three individuals just appeared at
the border of Kita Ward and Kawaguchi City!
They're clearly no ordinary civilians!
That's gotta be—
Displaying visuals!
That's them!
Ikusa, Meguru...
...and Knight!
You were right about full force.
She sent in three members
we've already faced?
Be careful! Unidentified enemies
might still be hiding.
Shinozaki, change criteria to "individuals
who suddenly emerged in Tokyo after midnight"!
Roger that...
Hang on! They've split up!
The woman and child are together.
And the man is alone.
Visuals confirmed. Continue monitoring.
It's decided then.
We'll make our move.
Wow.
Who knew...
I'd get to see you again so soon.
Must be my lucky day.
You two stand back for now.
You went out of your way to face me.
I'm assuming you're prepared to die.
He has the Water Utilization Right
and Adjustment Right...
I won't let him get away this time...
You're going down!
Tasuketsu: Fate of the Majority
Electroshock?!
What's going on?!
His Prime Right was Water Utilization!
Ya planning to attack me?!
Give it up, kid.
You can't use your Rejection Right
if I don't answer.
It's no use, Omi.
We're finished without Ryuta anyways.
Wha—
Even if we were to surrender,
you wouldn't let us go, would you?
'Course I wouldn't.
You're all dead.
Then the least I could do is—
Stop right there.
You're not getting any pity from me.
I wouldn't want you to warn your friends.
Actually, it's the opposite.
I figured I'd give you some information.
Information?
Fine then, go ahead.
But if you lie about anything
I'll consider it stalling.
Your friends will be the first to die,
so this better be good.
It's deets on Ebina and the man
with the Immobilization Right.
Immobilization?!
How do you know him?
Because we killed him.
And? What's your info?
Before that, promise you'll kill us
instantly without any suffering...
Deal?
If that's what you want...
An arm?!
Prioritize lightning rod!
My bad.
It took me a while to separate
the electro damage.
Ryuta! Your arm!
I focused all the damage and cut it off.
I'm virtually injury-free for now.
Nishime, nice work with
that lightning rod trick!
But be careful.
You don't want to expose yourself.
Jeez, don't scare me like that!
Omi and Nishime, back me up, will ya?
Raion, you stay low and
help us out if anything happens.
I'll try!
Let's go!
His electroshocks are always
preceded by a short spark.
If I could just time things right...
I can dodge them!
And besides...
He can only strike one blow at a time!
He could strike multiple directions
at once with Water Utilization,
but there's no sign of him using it.
Either there's no water supply
or he can't use it anymore.
Thought I wouldn't notice?
You idiot!
Damn it! I can't stop myself!
Take this!
I reject!
I figured you'd do that!
Prioritize!
Was that him?!
Is it a Right that changes trajectory?!
Gotcha! Your backside is wide open!
This was their plan all along!
Just kidding!
You both look so serious.
Here, let me show you a magic trick.
If I turn this ordinary
PET bottle upside down...
It froze! Is that his Right?!
It's a simple magic trick.
This is super-cooled water
that freezes instantly.
You could do it too.
Really?! Awesome!
Knight!
Now... I suppose that's enough fun.
Prime Right of Exchange!
Right back atcha!
I'm the one controlling the glass.
"Halt time within a one meter radius
when someone touches the water."
You saved me a lot of time
by falling for that so easily.
Now, you're the only one left, Knight-kun.
D-Damn you!
Prime Right of Destruc—
Just one second.
I have no desire to fight you.
I just wanted us to talk.
I had her take a nap
so we wouldn't be bothered.
Whaddya mean?
I don't think you're willingly
working for the Queen,
so I'd like to help you.
H-How did you know that?!
You really are an honest boy.
Can you tell me why you're
working for the Queen?
My mom and... my sister Lili
are being held hostage,
so I have to do as she says, or...
Your sister too?
Yeah, 'cause I lost to you guys last time...
She took another hostage because of one loss?
Perhaps the mother's life is already lost.
In that case...
Can I ask just one more question?
Is there someone named
Ren Iruga in your group?
Iruga...
You mean that blonde guy?
That's all I needed.
There's a way to save both
your mother and your sister,
but I need your help to do that.
What do you think?
R-Really?!
I'll do it! I'll help!
That's a good boy.
First is Lili-chan.
Can you lend me your ear?
That's all.
Did you memorize them?
Yeah, I got it!
The magic words are "Thank you"
and "Cock-a-Doodle-Doo".
All right then, close your eyes.
Induction Right.
I can't wait to hear the news,
both good and bad.
Man, Pres is amazing!
He took down two of
the Big Four all by himself!
You mean the "Three Powers".
You got the number and the name wrong!
But you sure it was okay?
Didn't we need at least one guy
to take us back to headquarters?
That was the initial plan, but Yagihashi
and I decided to change course.
This is fine.
So, Yagihashi. Any findings?
Just as you predicted, Sudo-kun.
Ren Iruga has joined the Queen's army.
Iruga's on the Queen's side?!
Shinozaki, change criteria to "individuals
who suddenly emerged in Tokyo after midnight"!
That's when he realized that
Iruga could suddenly appear
after hiding through space division?!
But we've taken down
a lot of enemies already.
And we're beating them in headcount.
R-Right!
Gokokuhotenji.
Keep displaying with the Presentation Right.
Yagihashi.
Our problem lies ahead. Isn't that right?
Lady Kisaragi, I have three
developments to report.
I'm listening.
Ren Iruga and Yohei Fukami have
disappeared beyond my surveillance.
But I have measures in place to respond.
The second development
pertains to our battles.
Ikusa, Meguru, and Knight
have all been killed.
The current Emperor
has sustained zero casualties.
I see.
And the third?
We were successful.
I hate to dampen the mood with sinister
predictions, but I'm confident about this.
If I'm correct, we should be receiving news
from Shinozaki-sensei any second now...
There's been a development!
Ikusa, Meguru, and Knight's
bodies have all disappeared!
Disappeared?!
Gokokuhotenji, display their bodies
with the Presentation Right.
Roger that!
Huh?
I can't display them?
Just as we thought... they've been concealed.
What do you mean "concealed"?
Looks like we're in the worst-case scenario.
Rise once again...
My loyal warriors.
And...
...the Emperor.
What do you mean "worst-case scenario"?!
Everything has panned out
according to Yagihashi's predictions.
Stay calm and listen up.
The Queen likely has the ability
to revive the dead.
Revive the dead?!
What's going on?!
Going back to the three
enemies we defeated...
You may recall how bodies
disappeared in the past.
The Emperor's Recovery Right!
The reason why the Presentation
Right doesn't work
is likely due to the Emperor's
Concealment Right.
The Emperor died, right?
Yes. He died and every Right
he possessed was left in limbo.
But what exactly does that mean?
It's not like they return
to their envelopes...
They went back to where they came from?
Precisely. Suppose they returned
to the "conscious world"...
There's only one way to re-materialize them
into our physical world.
Itako!
They're likely using Rights
formerly owned by the Emperor.
Which means it's almost certain
that the Queen is the itako.
To add on the Resurrection Right...
I was suspicious of why she'd send in people
we've faced, like Ikusa, in the first place.
There was a reason why she
had to recover their bodies.
Whether that was to
send them back into battle
or to intercept information is hard to say.
Either way, it adds up
if she can revive them.
No way...
They retreated during our first battle.
Perhaps they either couldn't revive
or recover them at that point.
In the most recent battle, Ikusa
used electricity rather than water.
I presume the Queen exchanged his Rights.
You mean they can come back
to life over and over again?!
And their Rights can be replaced each time?!
Sure, but there's no need to despair too much.
I've already planted a seed in Knight-kun.
Knight?
The Queen has a soft spot for children,
so he was the best candidate.
You know... You talk about the Queen
like you're acquaintances.
There's no way I'll let it slide now!
I know, I'll tell you now.
The Queen's name is Maria Kisaragi.
I believe she's 24 years old.
She's my cousin.
C-Cousin?!
On the second night of Tasuketsu,
I was revived in the nurse's office.
Right
I found the Suspension Right
waiting for me.
Day two was when all the men
were dead, besides Omi-kun.
Only a female individual
could have left the envelope.
Immediately, I realized it was her.
I assume it was her way of recruiting me.
Nevertheless, Tojuro Yagihashi chose
the side of the current Emperor...
I'm not exactly sure of her end goal, but...
Let us accept the Queen's challenge
to her heart's content.
Good grief...
We'll be breaking our backs now
with two eccentrics to entertain.
Man, this is boring!
At least we have snacks!
Jeez...
The Scenario
What a drag.